module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'What is the most widely eaten fish in the world?', 
    a: 'Herring',
    b: 'Tuna',
    c: 'Salmon',
    d: 'Bass',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtle wears red as his signature color?', 
    a: 'Leonardo',
    b: 'Michelangelo',
    c: 'Donatello',
    d: 'Raphael',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Cognac is a type of _____.', 
    a: 'Brandy',
    b: 'Whiskey',
    c: 'Vodka',
    d: 'Tequila',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'In cooking, what is "ghee"?', 
    a: 'Butter',
    b: 'Rice',
    c: 'A Vegetable',
    d: 'A Spice',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who is the mother of Sean Preston Federline?', 
    a: 'Jennifer Lopez',
    b: 'Christina Aguilera',
    c: 'Naomi Lowde-Priestley',
    d: 'Britney Spears',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following animals is an arthropod?', 
    a: 'Lizard',
    b: 'Squid',
    c: 'Spider',
    d: 'Fish',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which theme park was initially developed as a marketing vehicle for a brewing company?', 
    a: 'Gilroy Gardens',
    b: 'Knott\'s Berry Farm',
    c: 'Six Flags',
    d: 'Busch Gardens',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'General Motors uses which stock symbol?', 
    a: 'GENMO',
    b: 'GM',
    c: 'GEMO',
    d: 'GMOTO',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is a style of Japanese comic books and graphic novels, aimed at both adults and children?', 
    a: 'Naruto',
    b: 'Batsu',
    c: 'Manga',
    d: 'Getsuku',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the Canadia one-dollar coin called?', 
    a: 'Toonie',
    b: 'Loonie',
    c: 'Boonie',
    d: 'Doonie',
    answer: 'b'
  },
];